// Technology Questions
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A computer input device that is used to enter computer instructions and data into the computer.",
    answer: "Keyboard",
    options: [
      "Floppy disk",
      "Keyboard",
      "Monitor",
      "Flash drive"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "An output device that shows images and text from the computer.",
    answer: "Monitor",
    options: [
      "Desktop",
      "Modem",
      "Monitor",
      "Speaker"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A hand-held device that controls the cursor on the screen.",
    answer: "Mouse",
    options: [
      "Printer",
      "Keyboard",
      "Mouse",
      "Monitor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is not a browser?",
    answer: "IOS10",
    options: [
      "Chrome",
      "IOS10",
      "Internet Explorer",
      "Firefox"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The computer language used to write most web pages is known as",
    answer: "HTML",
    options: [
      "HDMI",
      "HTML",
      "NETL",
      "WEB"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "The_____________moves the cursor forward (right), one space at a time, leaving a blank space.",
  answer: "Spacebar",
  options: [
    "Control (CTRL)",
    "Enter/Return",
    "Spacebar",
    "Shift"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "____________turns capital letters on and off.",
  answer: "Caps Lock",
  options: [
    "Escape (ESC)",
    "Tab",
    "Control (CTRL)",
    "Caps Lock"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "The Internet is controlled by:",
  answer: "No one in particular.",
  options: [
    "The U.S. government.",
    "IBM, Intel, and Microsoft.",
    "No one in particular.",
    "The U.S. taxpayers."
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "Broadband connections include all of the following EXCEPT:",
  answer: "Telephone modems",
  options: [
    "Cable modems.",
    "Telephone modems",
    "Satellites",
    "DSL"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "DSL stands for:",
  answer: "Digital subscriber line.",
  options: [
    "Digital server lines.",
    "Digital subscriber line.",
    "Digits serviced per line.",
    "Damaged service line."
  ]
},

];
